Ralph C. Walker Papers
Ralph C. Walker Papers
1922-1961
Walker, Ralph C. (Ralph Curry), 1892-1962.
6.5 linear ft.
Papers of the American Baptist clergyman. Collection includes correspondence (1952-1961); travel journals (1922, 1934, 1956); sermons (1929-1961); photographs; church publications, and memorabilia.
148731
Biographical History
Ralph C. Walker (1892-1962) was an American Baptist minister. He may have been affiliated with the Euclid Ave. Baptist Church in Cleveland, Ohio.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Ralph C. Walker Papers consist of scrapbooks, correspondence, church publications, sermons, travel journals, and miscellany (including awards).
Arrangement of the Collection
All series are arranged chronologically.
Related Material
has numerous collections relating to church and clergy; please refer to for a complete listing. In addition, has made a concerted effort over the years to ensure that its manuscript and rare books holdings complement each other. As a result, many of our manuscript collections are supported by books, pamphlets, serials and other items which are cataloged in the Rare Books Collection. Please be sure to search for these related materials.
Subject and Genre Headings
Church and clergy; Walker, Ralph C. (Ralph Curry), 1892-1962 -- Archives.; Baptists -- Clergy.; Baptists -- United States.; Clergy -- United States.; Sermons, American.; Correspondence.; Diaries.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.; Sermons.; Clergy.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Scrapbooks
  - 1923-1938, 1952-1959, 6 folders, 1 volume (Box 1)
  - 1935, 1941-1952, 3 volumes (Oversize 1)
- Correspondence
  - 1952-1961, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Church publications
  - Weekly bulletins, 1952-1959 (Box 1)
  - Portland, Oregon, First Baptist Church audit, 1953 (Box 1)
  - The Trumpeter, 1949-1953; 4 volumes (Box 1)
  - Inspiration, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
- Sermons
  - 1950, 1958-1961, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - 1929, 59 folders (Box 1)
  - 1932, 27 folders (Box 1)
- Travel journals
  - 1922, 1934, 1956, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous
  - Sheet music by Walker, 1943 (Oversize 1)
  - Photographs, black and white, 1953 (Oversize 1)
  - Honorary Doctor of Divinity speech by George Taft, undated (Oversize 1)
  - Award, 1922-1961 (Oversize 1)